Hello, nice to run for the incubi.
To the eye we have a G-Line B-Line Pete Rat Goumai Kandai.
G-Line B-Line Pete Rat Goumai Kandai.
Let's like it open so he can breathe.
Hmm, fresh air.
Pete Rat, time to come here livey.
It's Gappy Deepa Kaki. It's Gappy Deepa Kaki.
Pete Rat eyes. Very bug and long. Very bug and long.
Deepa Tom eyes. Very flat.
Good boy. Very good boy.
Pete Rat eyes. Very good boy.
A rat-a-tat-tat-tat. A rat-a-tat-tat-tat. A rat-a-tat-tat-tat.
Smell my fine gear. Smell my fine gear.
I'm garving my Pete Rat a he had Masagi. A he had Masagi.
My Pete Rat has a strong Bungie cord. A strong Bungie cord.
I'm used to have nice Bungie cord. Snipe it off. Snipe.
Oh, I'm liking my Bungie cord. Eye ties. Cutie.
To to you ties I bow. To to you ties I bow.
I wonder if Pete Rat has a bra on. I wonder if Pete Rat has a bra on.
Let's find Oyut. Cutie open.
I think I found his bra on. I think I found his bra on.
I cannot pull it Oyut. Eye ties. Stuck insidey.
Bam bam bam bam bam...
Pi-a-ki! Pi-a-ki-o-yoo-t!